# ARKADIUSZ ZYGAN

JUNIOR FRONT-END DEVELOPER

#### CONTACT

+48 604 732 189 a.zygan@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/arkadiusz-zygan github.com/zyar3k zyar3k.github.io/portfolio

#### **PROFILE**

I have always been close to the IT. I'm fascinated by technological development that has been taking place extremely dynamically over the last several years. In 2019 I decided join into IT World deeper, professionally. The idea of learning to code has been grown in me for several years. I have been systematically learning front-end programming for a year. I'm also interested in web application design, I try to keep up with trends. I completed a 9-month programming supervised by an personal mentor -Bootcamp Web Developer Plus at Kodilla. In addition to the course I have completed interesting courses on the Udemy platform. I realize that a lot of work is ahead of me, which is why I train all the time and try to develop my skills. I focus on improving skills in JavaScript and React.

#### **TECHNOLOGY**

- HTML5
- CSS3
- SASS
- RWD
- Bootstrap
- Grid
- Flexbox
- AJAX
- API
- JavaScript ES5/ES6 z OOP
- ReactJs
- React Router
- Redux
- Node.js
- Express.js
- MongoDB Stack MERN

Tools:

GIT, NPM, Yarn, Webpack, Jira, VS Code

## новву

- IT (programming, new technologies)
- Psychology (social, cognitive, NLP)
- Music (rap, soundtrack, jazz)
- Sports (football, handball)

#### **SELECTED PROJECTS**

## **BettyCraftDesigns - online shop**

## https://github.com/Zyar3k/online\_shop\_bcd

Online store created from scratch. Application server and client. The ability to add products to your cart

#### Frontend:

react (cra), react-redux, react-thunk, axios, node-sass, styled-component, react-fontawesome
Backend:

cors, express, mongoose, nodemon

## cz@-app

#### https://youthful-clarke-0b8301.netlify.app/

Chat application from scratch - server and client

#### Used in project:

react, react-emoji, react-router-dom, socket.io-client, node-sass, cors, express, nodemon, socket.io

#### Must2Read

#### https://must2read.netlify.app/

A page with a list of recommended books. A list composed of lists recommended by 5 different sources.

#### Used in project:

react (cra), react-router-dom, axios, node-sass, cors, express, mongoose

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## Freelancer

England, Plymouth, 07.2016 - 04.2019

Self employment, cooperation with individual clients. First line of customer support. Supported industry:

- transport.

### 'ARO' Arkadiusz Zygan

Poland, southeastern part of the country 09.2008 - 06-2016

Self-employment - sales Representative, company-client cooperation. Industries served:

- construction.
- decorative.
- warehouse.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Jan Kochanowski University in Kielce, Master's degree

Pedagogy Rehabilitation 10.2004 - 06.2009

"I agree to the processing of personal data provided in this document for realising the recruitment process pursuant to the Personal Data Protection Act of 10 May 2018 (Journal of Laws 2018, item 1000) and in agreement with Regulation (EU) 2016/679 of the European Parliament and of the Council of 27 April 2016 on the protection of natural persons with regard to the processing of personal data and on the free movement of such data, and repealing Directive 95/46/EC (General Data Protection Regulation)"